<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ROS2 Foxy Packages on</title><link>https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2021-docs/advanced/software/</link><description>Recent content in ROS2 Foxy Packages on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2021-docs/advanced/software/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Overall presentation</title><link>https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2021-docs/advanced/software/presentation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2021-docs/advanced/software/presentation/</guid><description>Reachy&amp;rsquo;s software is composed of three main parts:
a HAL (Hardware Abstraction Layer) handling the communication with some of Reachy&amp;rsquo;s sensors i.e. the Dynamixel motors in the arms, fans, force sensors and Orbita actuator,
ROS packages: this is the core of the software. We are using ROS (Robotics Operating System), more precisely the ROS2 Foxy distribution, to interact with the HAL, to compute the kinematics for Reachy&amp;rsquo;s arms and Orbita, to get the camera feed and to manage the autofocus on Reachy&amp;rsquo;s motorised zooms.</description></item><item><title>Working with ROS2 Foxy</title><link>https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2021-docs/advanced/software/ros2-level/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2021-docs/advanced/software/ros2-level/</guid><description>Even if gRPC clients are available to control Reachy without knowing how to use ROS, you may want to work at the ROS level to implement new things for Reachy or use the tools provided by ROS. In this page, we will describe how to use the specfic ROS2 packages for Reachy.
Reachy runs natively on ROS2 Foxy. ROS stands for Robotic Operating System, it offers a huge variety of compatible algorithms and hardware drivers.</description></item><item><title>Reachy's configuration file</title><link>https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2021-docs/advanced/software/configuration-file/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2021-docs/advanced/software/configuration-file/</guid><description>We created a custom yaml file (~/.reachy.yaml) to indicate which Reachy&amp;rsquo;s configuration your robot has and whether a mobile base is connected to the robot or not. Having this file is useful to start only the necessary code required by the Reachy version you are using.
This file is read when Reachy&amp;rsquo;s main services are launched at boot.
The configuration file has two entries:
model: model of your Reachy (if it is a full kit, a starter kit, &amp;hellip;).</description></item></channel></rss>