<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ROS2 Foxy Packages on</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/advanced/ros2/</link><description>Recent content in ROS2 Foxy Packages on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/advanced/ros2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Working with ROS2 Foxy</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/advanced/ros2/introduction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/advanced/ros2/introduction/</guid><description>Reachy runs natively on ROS2 Foxy. ROS is a Robotic Operating System, it offers a huge variety of compatible algorithms and hardware drivers.
The embedded NUC computer comes with ROS2 and Reachy specific packages already installed and running. They provide full access to Reachy. You can:
get the /joint_state and publish joint goals use Rviz subscribe to various sensor topic (camera, force sensor, etc) access client for IK/FK While describing ROS or explaining how to use it is beyond the scope of this documentation (you should refer to the official documentation for that), we will describe the specfic ROS2 packages for Reachy and how to use them.</description></item><item><title>Reachy packages</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/advanced/ros2/packages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/advanced/ros2/packages/</guid><description>Reachy runs on ROS 2 version Foxy, which should now be installed and configured on your computer.
You have 2 main folders that contain all the packages you need to control Reachy.
reachy_ws/src folder This folder contains all the ROS packages used with Reachy:
reachy_msgs: https://github.com/pollen-robotics/reachy_msgs reachy_sdk_server: https://github.com/pollen-robotics/reachy_sdk_server reachy_controllers: https://github.com/pollen-robotics/reachy_controllers reachy_kinematics: https://github.com/pollen-robotics/reachy_kinematics dev folder This folder contains all the packages used with Reachy that are not based on ROS:</description></item><item><title>Which packages to use?</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/advanced/ros2/usage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/advanced/ros2/usage/</guid><description>If you have a Full kit, reachy_sdk_server.service is enabled by default, which means that all Reachy ROS2 packages are automatically launched when you start the robot (see section Using services for more information on the services).
What is running? You can check all ROS2 topics/services running on Reachy with:
ros2 topic list and
ros2 service list If you want finer control of which packages should run on your Reachy, see the section Using services.</description></item></channel></rss>