<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Content on</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/dashboard/content/</link><description>Recent content in Content on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/dashboard/content/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Debug</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/dashboard/content/debug/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/dashboard/content/debug/</guid><description>The debug page is the dashboard&amp;rsquo;s home page. It will indicate you if one of Reachy&amp;rsquo;s motor or force sensor is disconnected or if you forgot to turn on Reachy&amp;rsquo;s motors before booting its computer. Using this page is a good first step in debug if you are not able to connect to Reachy using the Python SDK or the VR for example.
Content In this page, one card will be created per Reachy&amp;rsquo;s part.</description></item><item><title>Dashboard</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/dashboard/content/dashboard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/dashboard/content/dashboard/</guid><description>The dashboard page is only accessible if the tools in the debug page found no missing motors or force sensors. It will allow you to get basic information from Reachy&amp;rsquo;s motors, change their compliance and control Reachy&amp;rsquo;s fans.
The page typically looks like the following:
It is composed of three parts:
Temperatures and positions displayer Compliance controller Fans controller Temperatures and positions displayer The displayer is composed of one card per robot part (either Left Arm, Right Arm or Head).</description></item><item><title>Wifi</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/dashboard/content/wifi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/dashboard/content/wifi/</guid><description>The wifi page of the dashboard lets you handle the network connection of the robot and typically looks like the following:
There are four main elements on this page:
Connection card: this card will display whether Reachy is connected to the Internet with an ethernet cable or a wifi network (in which case it will tell you which wifi network) or if it is using its hotspot,
Wifi adder card: this card will help you connect Reachy to a wifi network.</description></item><item><title>Services</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/dashboard/content/services/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/dashboard/content/services/</guid><description>The page services is dedicated to the services setup for Reachy. Working with services has the advantage of having Reachy&amp;rsquo;s code running automatically at boot whithout needing to open a terminal and start it yourself. However using the services can make debugging the robot more difficult because the code running for Reachy is &amp;ldquo;hidden&amp;rdquo;, that is why we made this page.
Having this page is useful when something is going wrong with Reachy.</description></item></channel></rss>