<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started on</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/sdk/getting-started/</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/sdk/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/sdk/getting-started/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 09:54:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/sdk/getting-started/introduction/</guid><description>The SDK in a nutshell The Python SDK lets you easily control and program a Reachy robot. It is used to read sensor information (eg. force sensor, camera image or joint position) and send actuator commands (eg. target position, turning on a fan).
It is designed to:
let you start controlling your robot in a few lines of codes, allow to focus on your application and not on hardware synchronisation issues, facilitate fast prototyping and iteration.</description></item><item><title>Installation</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/sdk/getting-started/install/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/sdk/getting-started/install/</guid><description>How to install the Python SDK The Python SDK is a pure Python library. The installation should thus be rather straightforward. It supports Python &amp;gt;= 3.6 (older versions may work but are not officially supported). It works on Windows/Mac/Linux.
We recommend to use virtual environment for your development. They make the installation simple and avoid compatibility issues. They also come with their pip command.
From PyPi pip3 install reachy-sdk From the source git clone https://github.</description></item><item><title>Finding Reachy's IP</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/sdk/getting-started/finding-ip/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 13:05:22 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/sdk/getting-started/finding-ip/</guid><description>The last required step before actually programing your Reachy is to find its IP address. A dedicated Find my IP section will give you more details on how to do that.
Note: Using the SDK locally also avoids network potential latency or bandwidth issue. Yet, it may not be as convenient as working directly from your usual laptop. You need to plug a screen, keyboard and mouse directly on Reachy&amp;rsquo;s computer.</description></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/sdk/getting-started/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 13:05:22 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/sdk/getting-started/hello-world/</guid><description>Now you should be able to connect to your Reachy and check that everything is ok. As we spoiled in the previous section, to connect to your robot, you simply need to run the following code:
from reachy_sdk import ReachySDK # Replace with the actual IP you've found. reachy = ReachySDK(host='the.reachy.ip.found.') Before diving into the next chapters that will guide you in the depth of what you can do with the Reachy SDK, here is a quick preview.</description></item></channel></rss>