<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>VR teleoperation app on</title><link>https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2021-docs/vr/use-teleop/</link><description>Recent content in VR teleoperation app on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2021-docs/vr/use-teleop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Commands</title><link>https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2021-docs/vr/use-teleop/commands/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2021-docs/vr/use-teleop/commands/</guid><description>Controllers input Input Action Valve Index HTC Vive Oculus Touch Controllers positions Controllers positions Controllers positions Reachy&amp;rsquo;s end effectors positions Trigger (squeeze) Trigger (squeeze) Index Trigger (squeeze) Open/Close adaptative gripper Trigger (press) Trigger (press) Trigger (press) Interact with UI Grip (squeeze) / Hand Trigger (squeeze) Open/Close adaptative gripper Right thumb stick (press) Right trackpad (press) Right thumb stick (press) Change commands type Right thumb stick (direction) Right trackpad (direction) Right thumb stick (direction) Select corresponding command A button (press) Menu button (press) A/X button (press) Click when required by the interface Both A buttons (press) Both menu buttons (press) Both A/X buttons (press) Emergency stop Thumb stick available command types:</description></item><item><title>Set Reachy ready</title><link>https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2021-docs/vr/use-teleop/prepare-robot/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2021-docs/vr/use-teleop/prepare-robot/</guid><description>To teleoperate Reachy from the same network If the computer used for the teleoperation app is connected to the same network as your robot, you only need to know your robot IP address.
💡 Don't know how to get it? Find out Reachy's IP address. To teleoperate Reachy remotely To teleoperate Reachy from another network, you need to create a redirection of an IP address towards your robot local IP address.</description></item><item><title>Teleoperate Reachy</title><link>https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2021-docs/vr/use-teleop/start/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2021-docs/vr/use-teleop/start/</guid><description>In brief Start teleoperating Reachy Make sure the robot is turned on, connected to the network and that all the robot&amp;rsquo;s services are running before launching the teleoperation application.
Enter your robot&amp;rsquo;s IP address on the computer at the launch of the app.
Turn the motors stiff in the menu for the robot to be able to move.
After having clicked &amp;ldquo;Validate my choices&amp;rdquo;, look straight ahead, with your body in the same orientation as your head while pressing A.</description></item><item><title>Emergency stop</title><link>https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2021-docs/vr/use-teleop/stop/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pollen-robotics.github.io/reachy-2021-docs/vr/use-teleop/stop/</guid><description>Activate emergency stop by clicking on:
both A buttons at the same time for Valve Index controllers both menu buttons for Vive controllers both A/X buttons for Oculus Touch. The following options are available:
Open grippers: immediately open the gripper as much as possible to enable the release of any object. Reduce torque: reduce the resistance of the arms motors. The arms will slighty fall down.</description></item></channel></rss>