<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>VR teleoperation app on</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/vr/use-teleop/</link><description>Recent content in VR teleoperation app on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/vr/use-teleop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>🚨 Best practice</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/vr/use-teleop/best-practice/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 13:05:22 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/vr/use-teleop/best-practice/</guid><description>👉🏾 This page contains really important information about the use of the teleoperation app. Please make sure you read it carefully before teleoperating Reachy. The teleoperation application use has nothing complicated, but you need to respect a few guidelines to avoid damaging the robot when using it. This page goes through the main elements you need to keep in mind while teleoperating Reachy. The guidelines are not exhaustive, but should give you a good start on how to use the application safely.</description></item><item><title>Commands (legacy version)</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/vr/use-teleop/old-commands/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/vr/use-teleop/old-commands/</guid><description>Controllers input Input Action Valve Index HTC Vive Oculus Touch Controllers positions Controllers positions Controllers positions Reachy&amp;rsquo;s end effectors positions Trigger (squeeze) Trigger (squeeze) Index Trigger (squeeze) Open/Close adaptative gripper Trigger (press) Trigger (press) Trigger (press) Interact with UI Grip (squeeze) / Hand Trigger (squeeze) Open/Close adaptative gripper Right thumb stick (press) Right trackpad (press) Right thumb stick (press) Change commands type Right thumb stick (direction) Right trackpad (direction) Right thumb stick (direction) Select corresponding command A button (press) Menu button (press) A/X button (press) Click when required by the interface Both A buttons (press) Both menu buttons (press) Both A/X buttons (press) Emergency stop Thumb stick available command types:</description></item><item><title>Controllers inputs</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/vr/use-teleop/commands/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/vr/use-teleop/commands/</guid><description>Oculus Quest Name Feature description (A) At robot teleoperation start: Validate position and start robot teleoperation During teleoperation: Return to menu (B) At robot teleoperation start: Cancel and return to menu (X) At robot teleoperation start: Validate position and start robot teleoperation During teleoperation: Return to menu (Y) At robot teleoperation start: Cancel and return to menu During teleoperation: Show/Hide state panel (control of robot&amp;rsquo;s temperature) Joystick left During teleoperation: Control mobile base direction Joystick right During teleoperation: Control antennas' emotion Index Trigger left In menu: Select button During teleoperation: Control left gripper Index Trigger right In menu: Select button During teleoperation: Control right gripper Middle finger Trigger left During teleoperation: Use translation mode for mobility Controller left position / orientation During teleoperation: Reachy&amp;rsquo;s left arm end effector position / orientation Controller right position / orientation During teleoperation: Reachy&amp;rsquo;s right arm end effector position / orientation Headset orientation During teleoperation: Reachy&amp;rsquo;s head orientation Valve Index Name Feature description (A) At robot teleoperation start: Validate position and start robot teleoperation During teleoperation: Return to menu (B) At robot teleoperation start: Cancel and return to menu left (B) only During teleoperation: Show/Hide state panel (control of robot&amp;rsquo;s temperature) Joystick left During teleoperation: Control mobile base direction Joystick right During teleoperation: Control antennas' emotion Index Trigger left In menu: Select button During teleoperation: Control left gripper Index Trigger right In menu: Select button During teleoperation: Control right gripper Controller left position / orientation During teleoperation: Reachy&amp;rsquo;s left arm end effector position / orientation Controller right position / orientation During teleoperation: Reachy&amp;rsquo;s right arm end effector position / orientation Headset orientation During teleoperation: Reachy&amp;rsquo;s head orientation See legacy version</description></item><item><title>Set Reachy ready</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/vr/use-teleop/prepare-robot/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/vr/use-teleop/prepare-robot/</guid><description>To teleoperate Reachy from the same network If the computer used for the teleoperation app is connected to the same network as your robot, you only need to know your robot IP address.
💡 Don't know how to get it? Find out Reachy's IP address. To teleoperate Reachy remotely To teleoperate Reachy from another network, you need to create a redirection of an IP address towards your robot local IP address.</description></item><item><title>Teleoperate Reachy</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/vr/use-teleop/start/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/vr/use-teleop/start/</guid><description>👉🏾 Before starting teleoperating Reachy, please make sure you read the Best Practice In brief Start teleoperating Reachy Make sure the robot is turned on, connected to the network and that all the robot&amp;rsquo;s services are running before launching the teleoperation application.
Select the robot you want to teleoperate (or create a new one), and click on &amp;ldquo;Connect&amp;rdquo;.
When the robot is ready, click on &amp;ldquo;Click here to start&amp;rdquo;, then look straight ahead, with your body in the same orientation as your head while pressing A to start the teleoperation.</description></item><item><title>Teleoperate Reachy (legacy)</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/vr/use-teleop/old-start/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/vr/use-teleop/old-start/</guid><description>👉🏾 Before starting teleoperating Reachy, please make sure you read the Best Practice In brief Start teleoperating Reachy Make sure the robot is turned on, connected to the network and that all the robot&amp;rsquo;s services are running before launching the teleoperation application.
Enter your robot&amp;rsquo;s IP address on the computer at the launch of the app.
Turn the motors stiff in the menu for the robot to be able to move.</description></item></channel></rss>