<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting started on</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/docs/getting-started/</link><description>Recent content in Getting started on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/docs/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Assemble mobile base + Reachy</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/docs/getting-started/mobile-base/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/docs/getting-started/mobile-base/</guid><description>Assembly tools You will need hex keys of size 3, 6 and 8. A mallet and a spring clip can be useful.
| | -- Unpacking your mobile base The mobile base is shipped in a custom box with its battery inside. The rest of the elements can be found in Reachy&amp;rsquo;s Box (including the poles and the battery charger).
⚠️ WARNING! ⚠️ To unpack the mobile base, remove the wood lid and use the internal handles as shown below.</description></item><item><title>Attach your robot without a mobile base</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/docs/getting-started/attach/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/docs/getting-started/attach/</guid><description>Full/Starter kit The first thing to do before using your Reachy Full or Starter kit is to attach it safely.
There are two options to do that:
Using the metal bar included in Reachy&amp;rsquo;s package Attach the metal bar to a table or a flat support using one of the metal fixation and screws:
If you don&amp;rsquo;t want to drill holes in your table, you can also use clamps between the table and the bottom part of the metal bar.</description></item><item><title>Turn on your robot</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/docs/getting-started/turn-on/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/docs/getting-started/turn-on/</guid><description>Full/Starter kit Connect the power supply to the robot (g) placement on the robot back interface.
Orbita neck needs to start in a straight position for its initialization. To do so, position the head so that Reachy looks straight ahead. (Don’t worry, the position doesn’t need to be exact, it just has to be correctly oriented).
You have two buttons behind the robot:
(a) : turn on/off Reachy’s embedded computer (h) : turn on/off alimentation of Reachy’s motors 👉 Turn on the motors with button (h) before starting the robot using button (a).</description></item><item><title>🆕 Connect to the dashboard</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/docs/getting-started/dashboard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/docs/getting-started/dashboard/</guid><description>Reachy Access Point (or RAP) is the name of the dashboard that we developed to give you an overview of the state of your Reachy (which motors are detected, what services are running, what are the motors temperatures&amp;hellip;) as well as giving you the possiblity to access quickly some features (changing a robot&amp;rsquo;s part compliance for example).
This tool has been thought to help you start easier with the robot and facilitate quick debugging.</description></item><item><title>Connect to your robot</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/docs/getting-started/connect/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/docs/getting-started/connect/</guid><description>Connect to the embedded computer For Full/Starter kit only:
Connect a screen, a mouse and a keyboard to Reachy.
👉 Password: reachy You can also access it via ssh. You will first need to know Reachy’s IP on your network. Then, using your own reachy-ip you can access it via:
ssh reachy@&amp;lt;reachy-ip&amp;gt; Don&amp;rsquo;t know what is your reachy-ip? Check out how to find the Reachy&amp;rsquo;s IP.
Check ROS is providing access to the topics Open a terminal on the computer, and enter:</description></item><item><title>Connect your robot to the network</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/docs/getting-started/network/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 15:21:01 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/docs/getting-started/network/</guid><description>Hard-wired connection For Full/Starter kit only:
Use an ethernet cable to connect your robot to the network. The ethernet plug is available at position (b) on Reachy’s hardware interface.
The computer inside Reachy is configured to use DHCP. It should thus be directly accessible on your network.
WiFi For Full/Starter kit only:
Reachy is equipped with a Wi-Fi module! You can then directly connect Reachy to your network wirelessly.
Note: if you are connected to Reachy remotely and depending on your use, we advise to favor an ethernet connection to benefit from a more stable connection.</description></item></channel></rss>