<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reachy system on</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/help/system/</link><description>Recent content in Reachy system on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/help/system/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Finding Reachy's IP</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/help/system/find-my-ip/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 13:05:22 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/help/system/find-my-ip/</guid><description>There is a few option to find Reachy&amp;rsquo;s IP. It depends on your setup and how you want to use it.
Working directly on Reachy You can run the SDK directly on Reachy&amp;rsquo;s computer. In this case, the IP is the localhost address: &amp;ldquo;127.0.0.1&amp;rdquo;.
Via the network First, you need to make sure that both Reachy and the computer you want to use for the SDK are on the same network.</description></item><item><title>Check which motors are connected</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/help/system/discovery-tool/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 13:05:22 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/help/system/discovery-tool/</guid><description>Reachy&amp;rsquo;s SDK Server might not work due to a motor that have been disconnected during transportation or manipulation. Knowing which motors are actually detected by Reachy&amp;rsquo;s software is really useful for debug.
Stopping the running service First of all, you need to stop the service running. If you have not modified the default service, open a terminal and enter:
sudo systemctl stop reachy_sdk_service.service Running the discovery Then you can run the discovery python script to detect the connected motors.</description></item><item><title>Disconnected force sensor</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/help/system/reconnect-load-sensor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 13:05:22 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/help/system/reconnect-load-sensor/</guid><description>Each arm of Reachy is equipped with a load sensor to measure how much force is applied by the gripper to the object. It allows to know when the gripper is holding an object.
The load sensor is in two part: the sensor itself and an electronic board reading its values and connected to Reachy&amp;rsquo;s internal computer.
The sensor is placed between the two 3D printed pieces composing Reachy&amp;rsquo;s gripper.</description></item><item><title>Orbita blue LED</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/help/system/orbita-blue-led/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 13:05:22 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/help/system/orbita-blue-led/</guid><description>The Orbita actuator is equipped with a blue LED which gives information about its state.
The LED can have three behaviors:
the LED is off: Reachy&amp;rsquo;s software is running,
the LED is on and not blinking: Orbita&amp;rsquo;s motors are turned on but Reachy&amp;rsquo;s software is not started,
the LED is blinking: it indicates an Orbita safety shutdown due to the motors overheat. This usually happens when the motor are forcing.</description></item><item><title>Plugging back a cable of Reachy's arm motor</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/help/system/reconnect-motor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 13:05:22 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/help/system/reconnect-motor/</guid><description>During manipulation or transportation, a motor cable of Reachy&amp;rsquo;s arm might get disconnected.
An unplugged cable can be spotted more or less easily in each part of an arm, except for the shoulder pitch motor inside Reachy&amp;rsquo;s torso which is a bit harder.
A typical arm of Reachy is composed of eight motors. The motors are connected as a chain starting with the shoulder pitch. Each motor is connected to the motors located before and after it in the chain.</description></item><item><title>Reachy's computer is not running</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/help/system/computer-not-running/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 13:05:22 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/help/system/computer-not-running/</guid><description>Reachy&amp;rsquo;s computer is off, even after pressing the on button When you power your robot and turn on both the motors and Reachy&amp;rsquo;s computer, you might have Reachy&amp;rsquo;s computer still not turned on.
There are two ways to check this:
check Reachy&amp;rsquo;s computer power button If the computer is turned on, there should be a round white led around the button brighting.
check if the computer fan is running To do that, first lower Reachy&amp;rsquo;s tee-shirt, on the front side you should see something like this:</description></item></channel></rss>