<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docs on</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Docs on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Software installation process</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/docs/installation/full-installation-process/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 08:43:34 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/docs/installation/full-installation-process/</guid><description>You decided to buy a Full/Starter kit, congratulations! You just saved a lot of time ;)
Everything you need is already installed on your robot.
Of course you may want to know what&amp;rsquo;s included in it. Please refer to section What is running/What can I run on my robot for more information.
For Arm kit only:
I have an Arm kit. What do I need to do?</description></item><item><title>Use Reachy SDK</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/docs/installation/use-sdk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 10:46:05 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/docs/installation/use-sdk/</guid><description>If you want to control Reachy using its Python SDK, you only need to install it on the computer you want to use. The SDK is a pure Python library so it can be easily installed on any computer running Python &amp;gt;= 3.6.
from reachy_sdk import ReachySDK reachy = ReachySDK(host='reachy.IP.address') Ready to start using the Python SDK? Check out the Python SDK documentation!
Getting started with Reachy Python SDK</description></item><item><title>Use VR teleoperation app</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/docs/installation/use-vr/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 10:46:05 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/docs/installation/use-vr/</guid><description>Reachy 2021 is fully compatible with the VR teleoperation application. You do not need to install anything else on your robot.
Please refer to the teleoperation application documentation for the installation details on the remote computer.
Getting started with Reachy VR teleoperation app</description></item><item><title>Update packages</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/docs/update/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/docs/update/</guid><description>Fetch repositories on Github Desktop All the Github repositories of Reachy&amp;rsquo;s packages are cloned on Github Desktop. Simply find it on Reachy&amp;rsquo;s computer, select one by one the repositories and fetch to check if there are updates. Pull the changes in case updates are found.
The list of all Reachy&amp;rsquo;s packages which may require updates is available here:
Find Reachy packages list 👉 In case of major Reachy updates, it may happen some packages of the list are not cloned on your robot.</description></item><item><title>Arm kit software installation</title><link>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/docs/installation/arm-installation-process/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 08:43:34 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.pollen-robotics.com/docs/installation/arm-installation-process/</guid><description>You decided to buy an Arm kit, you have a few things to install on your computer. Don’t worry, we will go step by step to guide you through the installation process!
What do I need? To program and control your robot, you have two main options:
Directly control it via ROS2 Foxy: this gives you lower level access to the robot and full interoperability with ROS. Yet ROS can be complex, so if you are not familiar with it, that’s probably not what you are looking for.</description></item></channel></rss>